A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.25 (A99) FA477
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A99), 1974-1999; 1.25; 99.6 Cubic Feet; 83 standard record storage cartons. Boxes R3191-R3252, R3266-R3286.
  - Population Sciences (PS)
    - PS 9414 - JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY - CORPUS LUTEUM, 1988-1995 (Box R3278)
    - 94-8120-23 - ALL INDIA INSTITUTE OF MEDICAL SCIENCES - INTERNATIONAL MEETING ON CELL SIGNALLING AND IMPLANTATION, 1993-1996, 1999 (Box R3278)
    - 94-8120-23 - WAYS OF KNOWING, INC. - DOCUMENTARY FILM ON RU486 IN DEVELOPING WORLD, 1994 (Box R3278)
    - PS 9430 - ORGANIZACAO INTERNATIONAL DE PESQUISA EM SAUDE REPRODUCTIVA (BRAZIL) - BC CONFERENCE: INTRODUCTION OF EMERGENCY CONTRACEPTION IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1994-1996 (Box R3278)
    - PS 9431 - UNIVERSITY OF CHILE - RESEARCH INSTITUTE FOR MOTHER AND CHILD - UNIPLANT, 1994-1995, 1999 (Box R3278)
    - PS 9437 - CENTER FOR REPRODUCTIVE LAW AND POLICY - INTERNATIONAL PROGRAM ON REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH RIGHTS, 1992-1997; 2 folders. (Box R3279)
    - PS 9504 - ASOCIACION DOMINICANA PRO-BIENESTAR DE LA FAMILIA (DOMINICAN REPUBLIC) - 14TH MEETING OF LATIN AMERICAN ASSOCIATION FOR RESEARCH ON HUMAN REPRODUCTION, 1994-1995 (Box R3279)
    - PS 9507 - AUSTRALIAN NATIONAL UNIVERSITY - SEMINAR ON DEMOGRAPHIC TRANSITION, 1993-1996 (Box R3279)
    - PS 9507 - AUSTRALIAN NATIONAL UNIVERSITY - SEMINAR ON DEMOGRAPHIC TRANSITION - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R3279)
    - PS 9511 - MONTEFIORE MEDICAL CENTER - EFFECTS OF CALCIUM CHANNEL BLOCKERS ON MALE FERTILITY, 1995 (Box R3279)
    - PS 9512 - CENTRE FOR DEVELOPMENT AND POPULATION ACTIVITIES - PARTICIPATION IN 1995 WORLD CONFERENCE ON WOMEN, 1995-1996 (Box R3279)
    - PS 9513 - COMMUNICATIONS CONSORTIUM MEDIA CENTER - PRESERVE CAIRO CONSENSUS AT WOMEN'S CONFERENCE IN BEIJING, 1995-1996 (Box R3279)
  - International Relations (IR)
    - IR 8614 - COUNCIL ON FOREIGN RELATIONS - EUROPEAN-AMERICAN RELATIONS, 1982-1995 (Box R3280)
    - IR 8614 - COUNCIL ON FOREIGN RELATIONS - EUROPEAN-AMERICAN RELATIONS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R3280)
  - International Security (IS)
    - IS 9210 - MASSACHUSETTS INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY - NUCLEAR PROLIFERATION IN THE MIDDLE EAST, 1990-1996 (Box R3280)
    - IS 9315 - CARNEGIE ENDOWMENT FOR INTERNATIONAL PEACE - PARTICIPATION OF ASIAN SCHOLARS AT NON-PROLIFERATION CONFERENCE, 1993-1996 (Box R3280)
    - IS 9322 - CENTRO DE INVESTIGACIONES EUROPEO LATINOAMERICANAS (ARGENTINA) - ORAL HISTORY OF NUCLEAR PLAN, 1991-1995, 1999 (Box R3280)
    - IS 9328 - STIMSON CENTER - ELIMINATING WEAPONS OF MASS DESTRUCTION, 1993-1997 (Box R3280)
    - IS 9402 - HELLENIC FOUNDATION FOR DEFENSE AND FOREIGN POLICY - SUPPORT PARTICIPATION IN HALKI SEMINAR SERIES, 1992-1996, 1999 (Box R3280)
    - 94-8210-4 - EDUCATIONAL FOUNDATION FOR NUCLEAR SCIENCE - INTERNET PROJECT, 1994-1995, 1999 (Box R3280)
    - 94-8210-14 - STANFORD UNIVERSITY - 1995 CARMEL ROUNDTABLE OF ASIA-PACIFIC LEADERS, 1994, 1997 (Box R3280)
    - IS 9419 - BROWN UNIVERSITY- CUBAN MISSILE CRISIS AFFECT ON NUCLEAR PROLIFERATION, 1991-1996 (Box R3280)
    - IS 9420 - HERBERT SCOVILLE JR. PEACE FELLOWSHIP - 1995 FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM, 1994-1995, 1999 (Box R3281)
    - IS 9501 - CENTER FOR STRATEGIC AND INTERNATIONAL STUDIES, INC. - KOREAN PENINSULA MILITARY ISSUES, 1994-1996 (Box R3281)
    - IS 9505 - CENTER FOR STRATEGIC AND INTERNATIONAL STUDIES, INC. - "NUCLEAR WEAPONS IN A TRANSFORMED WORLD", 1994-1997 (Box R3281)
    - IS 9514 - INTERNATIONAL PHYSICIANS FOR THE PREVENTION OF NUCLEAR WAR - PARTICIPATION OF NORTH KOREAN AND CHINESE PHYSICIANS AT 1995 HIROSHIMA CONFERENCE, 1994-1995 (Box R3281)
    - IS 9518 - WILTON PARK (ENGLAND) - PARTICIPATION IN CONFERENCE ON CRISIS MANAGEMENT AND CONFIDENCE BUILDING IN SOUTH ASIA, 1995 (Box R3281)
  - Special Interests and Explorations (SIE)
    - SIE 8830 - SOUTHERN AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT COORDINATION CONFERENCE - AMBASSADORS SEMINAR, 1988-1997 (Box R3281)
    - SIE 9310 - HERITAGE COLLEGE - INDIAN CHILD WELFARE CURRICULUM, 1992-1997 (Box R3281)
    - SIE 9313 - WGBH EDUCATIONAL FOUNDATION- SERIES ENTITLED "AFRICANS IN AMERICA", 1992-1998 (Box R3281)
    - SIE 9314 - FUNDS FOR THE COMMUNITY'S FUTURE - ESTABLISHING A NATIONAL OFFICE, 1993-1995 (Box R3281)
    - SIE 9318 - AMERICAN ACADEMY OF ARTS AND SCIENCES - TRAINING ARABS AND ISRAELIS TO WORK TOGETHER, 1993-1996 (Box R3281)
    - SIE 9321 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - ABILITY OF U.S. GOVERNMENT TO ADDRESS DOMESTIC ISSUES, 1992-1995 (Box R3281)
    - SIE 9404 - MAYNARD INSTITUTE FOR JOURNALISM EDUCATION - MAYNARD MEMORIAL PROJECT, 1993-1994 (Box R3282)
    - 94-8040-5 - INSTITUTE FOR PUERTO RICAN POLICY - NEW YORK CITY LATINO NONPROFIT SECTOR PROJECT, 1994-1995 (Box R3282)
    - SIE 9416 - THIRTEEN/WNET- DOCUMENTARY ON YOUTH VIOLENCE IN AMERICA, 1994-1996 (Box R3282)
    - 94-8040-19 - UNITED STATES - INDOCHINA RECONCILIATION PROJECT OF THE FUND FOR RECONCILIATION AND DEVELOPMENT - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1994 (Box R3282)
    - 94-8040-20 - PRIVATE AGENCIES COLLABORATING TOGETHER (PACT) - CAMBODIA PROGRAM TO STRENGTHEN THE NGO SECTOR, 1993-1994 (Box R3282)
    - 94-8040-22 - NATIONAL LATINO COMMUNICATIONS CENTER - SERIES "CHICANO HISTORY OF THE MEXICAN-AMERICAN CIVIL RIGHTS MOVEMENT", 1990, 1993-1997 (Box R3282)
    - 94-8040-24 - VICTIM SERVICES - DOMESTIC VIOLENCE IN UNITED STATES, 1994-1996 (Box R3282)
    - SIE 9429 - OVERSEAS DEVELOPMENT COUNCIL - WORLD BANK'S ROLE IN IMPROVING STATUS OF WOMEN, 1994-1996 (Box R3282)
    - SIE 9430 - PHILANTHROPIC INITIATIVE, INC. - GOING-TO-SCALE PROJECT, 1994-1998; 2 folders. (Box R3282)
    - SIE 9431 - PEKING UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - CHINA CENTER FOR ECONOMIC RESEARCH, 1994-1995 (Box R3282)
    - SIE 9505 - FOREIGN POLICY ASSOCIATION - PUBLIC EDUCATION, 1994-1996 (Box R3282)
    - SIE 9508 - STATE UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK - ROCKEFELLER INSTITUTE OF GOVERNMENT - NEW YORK STATE COMMISSION ON CONSTITUTIONAL REVISION, 1995 (Box R3282)
  - Special Interests (SI)
    - SI 9201 - FOREIGN ASSISTANCE - FUTURE OF - SII PROGRAM OPERATIONS, 1992-1994 (Box R3283)
    - SI 9517 - FOUNDATION IN SUPPORT OF THE UNITED NATIONS - COMMITTEE FOR THE '95 WORLD CONFERENCE ON WOMEN, 1995 (Box R3283)
    - SI 9520 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR DIARRHOEAL DISEASE RESEARCH (BANGLADESH) - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1995-1996, 1999 (Box R3283)
  - Special Programming (SP)
    - SP 8804 - CENTRE FOR ECONOMIC POLICY RESEARCH (LONDON) - NORTH-SOUTH MACROECONOMIC INTERACTIONS WORKSHOP, 1988-1994, 1998 (Box R3283)
    - SP 9103 - INTERNATIONAL FOOD POLICY RESEARCH INSTITUTE - HOUSEHOLD RESOURCES WORKSHOP, 1991-1994 (Box R3283)
  - African Initiatives (AI)
    - AI 9204 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - SOUTHERN AFRICAN MOOT COURT COMPETITION, 1992-1995 (Box R3283)
    - AI 9208 - THIRD WORLD ORGANIZATION FOR WOMEN IN SCIENCE (TWOWS) - AFRICAN WOMEN PARTICIPATION IN CONFERENCE, 1992-1995 (Box R3283)
    - AI 9213 - CENTRE FOR ADVANCED SOCIAL SCIENCE - INSTITUTIONAL DEVELOPMENT, 1992-1997 (Box R3283)
    - AI 9215 - DEVELOPMENT RESOURCES CENTRE - SUPPORT SANGONET NETWORK, 1992-1996 (Box R3283)
    - AI 9217 - INSTITUTE FOR A DEMOCRATICAL TERNATIVE FOR SOUTH AFRICA (IDASA) - COSTS OF PARTICIPANTS FROM SOUTH AFRICAN COUNTRIES AT ECONOMIC CONFERENCE, 1992-1995 (Box R3284)
    - AI 9220 - ASSOCIATION OF AFRICAN UNIVERSITIES - HIGHER EDUCATION IN AFRICA, 1992-1996 (Box R3284)
    - AI 9309 - CLARK UNIVERSITY - BIBLIOGRAPHY OF AFRICAN ENVIRONMENTAL PUBLICATIONS, 1993-1995, 1998 (Box R3284)
    - AI 9310 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - BASIC EDUCATION DATA IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1993-1995 (Box R3284)
    - AI 9311 - AFRICAN CENTRE FOR COMMUNICATIONS AND DEVELOPMENT (ACCD) (KENYA) - TELEVISION PROGRAMS RELATING TO PROBLEMS OF AFRICAN TEENAGERS, 1991-1996 (Box R3284)
    - 94-8140-1 - WORLD PRIORITIES - REVISED EDITION OF WOMEN ...A WORLD SURVEY, 1994-1996 (Box R3284)
    - 94-8140-2 - IOWA STATE UNIVERSITY - PLANNING WORKSHOP OF INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF THEORETICAL AND APPLIED PHYSICS, 1994-1995 (Box R3284)
    - AI 9403 - NORTHWESTERN UNIVERSITY - CONFERENCE ON AFRICAN FARMERS AND THEIR ENVIRONMENT, 1993-1996 (Box R3284)
    - AI 9407 - MICHIGAN STATE UNIVERSITY - ACADEMIC LINKAGES IN SOUTH AFRICA, 1994-1996 (Box R3284)
    - AI 9502 - AFRICAN ASSOCIATION OF POLITICAL SCIENCE (ZIMBABWE) - 10TH BIENNIAL CONGRESS, 1994-1996 (Box R3284)
    - AI 9503 - UNIVERSITY OF PRETORIA (SOUTH AFRICA) - 1995 ALL-AFRICA MOOT COURT COMPETITION, 1995-1996 (Box R3284)
    - AI 9507 - AFRICAN-AMERICAN INSTITUTE - WORKSHOP TO PROMOTE FEMALE EDUCATION AGENDA, 1995 (Box R3284)
  - School Reform (SR)
    - SR 9210 - HUNTER COLLEGE- BLACK SCHOOL SUPERINTENDENTS RETREAT, 1991-1995 (Box R3284)
    - SR 9306 - UNIVERSITY OF TENNESSEE (KNOXVILLE) - NETWORK FOR INNOVATIVE SCHOOLS OF EDUCATION, 1991-1997 (Box R3284)
    - SR 9401 - MANPOWER DEMONSTRATION RESEARCH CORP. - SITE DEVELOPMENT, TECHNICAL ASSISTANCE AND TRAINING, AND RESEARCH ACTIVITIES, 1993-1998; 2 folders. (Box R3285)
    - 94-8030-6 - PUBLIC AGENDA FOUNDATION - "VALUES IN THE SCHOOLS: FINDING AN AMERICAN CONSENSUS", 1994-1995 (Box R3285)
    - 94-8030-7 - ARIZONA STATE UNIVERSITY - COALITION TO INCREASE MINORITY DEGREES' ANNUAL CONFERENCE, 1994-1995 (Box R3285)
    - 94-8030-10 - FUND FOR NEW YORK CITY PUBLIC EDUCATION COMMISSION ON EDUCATIONAL STANDARDS AND ACCOUNTABILITY, 1994-1997 (Box R3285)
    - 94-8030-11 - PUBLIC EDUCATION ASSOCIATION - RESTRUCTURE PUBLIC EDUCATION IN TWO SCHOOL DISTRICTS IN NEW YORK CITY, 1994-1997 (Box R3285)
    - SR 9412 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - EDUCATIONAL AUDIT OF NEW HAVEN PUBLIC SCHOOLS, 1993-1997 (Box R3285)
    - SR 9413 - FUND FOR NEW YORK CITY PUBLIC EDUCATION - COMER PROGRAM IN BROOKLYN'S COMMUNITY SCHOOL DISTRICT #13, 1994-1996 (Box R3285)
    - SR 9501 - PUBLIC BROADCASTING SERVICE - TECHNOLOGY-BASED PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT SERVICE FOR K-12 EDUCATORS, 1992-1996; 2 folders. (Box R3285)